What? You wanna take back your move again?
No way, you've taken back too many moves already.
Chu Feng.
This game today,
let me teach you a lesson.
Don't always focus on winning or losing.
Watch the path beneath your feet.
Got it?
Sir,
I'll remember that.
Next time, I'll do better.
Just give me another chance.
Qin Mo!
His old condition is acting up.
Quick, drink this.
Sir,
how many times have I told you?
You need to make time to see a doctor.
Just an old problem, I'm fine.
That's enough.
Stop bickering, you two.
He's a sore loser.
Sir,
if you're not convinced, let's play another round.
He won't admit defeat.
One more round.
Come on, one more game.
One more.
Congratulations.
You got into grad school.
Pepper spray.
Aren't you always teasing me,
calling me a tomboy?
Do I really need this?
I'd scare off any creeps myself.
Better safe than sorry.
That's thoughtful of you.
I'll take it.
Chen Hui!
If you're a real man,
let Siqi go.
Come at me if you want to kill someone!
Dying such a dramatic death,
you two should be satisfied.
Siqi!
What's the situation on Chu Feng's side?
Arriving shortly.
Sir!
Squad assembled and ready.
Chief, how's Sun Bo?
He was ambushed by Ma Xiaojun.
He didn't make it.
The mission Sun Bo couldn't finish,
we'll finish for him.
Pull yourself together, Chu Feng.
Everyone, stay sharp.
This is the most critical moment.
Just hold on a little longer,
and we can close the net.
And all of you, keep this in mind.
Everyone here
has your back.
Yes, sir!
Sir.
All personnel assembled.
Based on drone surveillance,
there are three people inside the building.
Most likely Chen Hui,
Yu Tianfang, and He Siqi.
Copy that.
Proceed as planned.
Everyone,
left face!
Move out!
Left face!
Double time, march!
All units, take positions! All units, take positions!
Until you receive the signal,
do not enter the factory.
We can't risk harming the hostages.
Once the order is given,
initiate the rescue operation immediately.
Qin Mo,
don't act on your own.
Don't worry.
I won't get in your way.
Move out!
All units, listen up.
Flank them by sectors,
and close in layer by layer.
Use your radios
to report your positions in real time.
Your teammates
and backup units
are ready to back you up.
Tighten the perimeter
as much as possible.
Tighten the perimeter as much as possible!
Qin Mo!
Get the fire department here, fast!
Chu Feng!
Watch out!
Dispatch, we need the fire department.
We need support at the West Warehouse.
Chen Hui!
There's nowhere to run!
Bet you didn't know this, did you?
We found your son.
Don't you dare bring my son into this!
You worthless piece of trash!
You got your own mentor killed!
Come catch me if you have the guts!
Chen Hui,
turn yourself in now,
and you might still get to see your son.
I really appreciate your concern.
Chen Hui!
Drop the gun!
I won't let you get away with this.
Call an ambulance, hurry!
I'm fine.
I'm just a little tired.
I want to sleep.
Don't sleep!
Stay awake, please!
Think about the happiest moments
we shared together.
Every day I spent with you,
I was so happy.
From the resort to the restaurant
And then to the butcher shop
I kept doing worse and worse
yet you still fell for a loser like me.
Only now do I realize
I'm the luckiest person alive
I used up all my luck
Just to meet you
I'm the one who's lucky.
Meeting you
made me realize
What true love really is
Love isn't about possession,
or control.
It's wanting the absolute best for them,
and making them happy.
I can't live without you
Silly
I'm never going to leave you
After all, I'm
the absolute most
badass woman in the world.
No, you can't go in
I can't breathe
What's wrong?
Come on, take a rest
Just rest for a bit
Watch over her
I'll go get a doctor
Patient has a thigh laceration
Severe blood loss
Blood pressure 60 over 30
Heart rate 140
O2 sats undetectable
Set up two IV lines.
Four units of red cells and normal saline
One milligram of epinephrine, IV push
Found the femoral artery rupture
Hand me a hemostat, quick!
She's in V-fib! Heart stopped!
Blood pressure unreadable.
Get the defibrillator, now!
Alright, everybody clear!
Ready!
Clear, shock!
Where's Qibao?
Where is Qibao?
You're hurt,
you need to rest.
My wife saved my life
I have to go see her right now
Come on, take me to her
Let's go!
No,
Where is Qibao?
What... what are you doing?
Doctor
How is she?
We did everything we could
I'm sorry
Siqi